

Contact

- Phone
 +6394612073
- Email francissarabia01433@gmail.com
- Address

 Batangas City, Philippines

Expertise

- Amazon Product Research
- Computer Literate
- Adobe Photoshop
- Canya
- Scheduling
- Virtual Assistant

Language

Filipino ——— English

FRANCIS EJ SARABIA

GENERAL VIRTUAL ASSITANT / EXECUTIVE ASSITANT GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Objective

I am Virtual assistant providing remote assistance to business management professionals by using my exceptional expertise in handling administrative, graphic design and clerical work from remote location. My roles are includes conducting research and organizing data, interacting with customers or clients using graphic designs and performing additional clerical duties like updating calendars or sorting documents.

Experience

PART TIME JOBS

AMAZON PRODUCT RESEARCH

Dr. Squatch Store

February 2020 - December 2021

The company develop and produce natural, high-performance personal care products specifically designed to meet the demands of men everywhere.

GENERAL VIRTUAL ASSISTANT

Upwork

January 2020 - March 2021

As a general virtual assistant I performed various administrative tasks, including answering emails, scheduling meetings and making travel arrangements. Moreover, creating documents, presentation, data entry and graphic design.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Upwork

September 2021 - December 2021

I worked as a part-time graphic designer to a client on Upwork, and made him a design for ads on a mobile application he created.

FULL TIME JOBS

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

MODULE ENTERPRISES
February 2018 - January 2020

As a full time employee to a design and printing business, I assigned to create a layout out of my skills and creativity and based to my client needs. I can design layout for different occasions such as birthdays, anniversary, wedding, invitations etc.

Education

2019 - present

Batangas State University

BS Information Technology

The Batangas State University is a Level IV state university in the province of Batangas, Philippines. Established as a manual training school in 1903, Batangas State University is the oldest higher education institution in the country's Calabarzon Region.

COURSES AND TRAININGS

NC II COMPUTER SYSTEM SERVICING 2018

TESDA

AMAZON DROPSHIPPING 2019

Your VA Buddy

BASIC PRODUCT RESEARCH 2019

Your VA Buddy

BASIC FOUNDATION AND TOOLS SMM 2022

Surge

FACEBOOK ADS MARKETING TRAINING

2022 *Surge*

REFERENCES

CHRISTINE GHIA

FREE LANCER christineghia@gmail.com